Don't rush into the attic
The lost life never comes back, drive slowly..
There is someone awaiting for you.
Your family is waiting you at home..
Death comes to whom?
When it comes?
No one knows.....
Speed, rash driving is signal to death,
Do you need such a pain?
Don't drive by breaking the traffic rules
Rules are not just meant for fine
Is your life not even have a worth of 100rs?!!...
Oh human.. one who is fearing for fine,
Don't you need your life?
After losing body parts,
Tell me... how will you live??!!..
You are the only supportive to your family...
Though it is a bad road...
driving with negligancy..
drink and drive...
Using moblie while driving..
No helmet wearing is
Calling for death
Why so hurry
if went five minutes late?
Be careful
Lost body parts won't come back once it is gone
Don't rush into the attic
The lost life never comes back, drive slowly..
Be careful and go slowly..
Follow all the traffic rules..
Wish everyone well..
Everyone Live a peaceful life.
Be careful and go slowly..
Follow all the traffic rules..
Wish everyone well..
Everyone Live a peaceful life.
We have a lifespan of few days,
live it happily.
Fight and overcome all sort of difficulties.
To live the life of tomorrow happily
Today's safety behaviour shows the way.